Hey friends, welcome to your own
channel and online zone. Friends,
if you have taken any work
insurance from Paasi Bazaar and for some reason you have not
added the nominee while taking the insurance, then
today in our video it will be
told how
after taking insurance from Paasi Bazaar,
you can add, change or
update your nominee.
For this, first of all you have to open Google in your mobile,
after that you have to search by
typing Paasi Bazaar in the search box.
On searching,
some links related to Paasi Bazaar will appear in the search results.
After looking at all these links, go down a little on the page. You will
find the link of the official website of Policy Bazaar here. You have to touch this link.
In a short while, the official website of Paasi Bazaar will
open. Here
you have to touch on the sign in type, after that
fill in the registered mobile number here, after that
touch on the sign in with OTP type, an OTP will be sent to your registered mobile number, after
checking that OTP with your registered mobile number, enter the
OTP here.  After filling it, you have to touch the confirm OTP tape. In
this way,
in a short time, you will be logged into your Policy Bazaar account.
In your Policy Bazaar account page, you will
find the account tag on the right top corner. You have to touch this type. On touching it,
a drop down will appear. From this drop down,
you have to touch the type with "Mi Policy". A
list of all the policies you have taken on Policy Bazaar will appear here. To
change it, you have to touch the "Get Help" type in front of it.
After that, below here, you have to touch the "Change
Required in Policy Details" type. On
touching it, the page will open in this manner.
Go down a little in the space.
After the nature appears, you have to touch the "Ownership Details"
type.
On touching the "Ownership Details" type,
a drop down will appear. Tick the
check box in front of the thing you want to change from the drop down.
After that, go down a little in the page
and touch the "Proceed" type.
A new page will open
here.  The
details of the old registered nominee will appear.
Check the details of the old name.
If you want to change something,
touch on change in front of the details.
After that, go down a little on the page.
Here you have to fill in the name of the nominee for your policy.
Now you have to touch here. A drop down will
appear. From the drop down,
select the relation which you have with the name nominee.
After making the relationship, touch on the proceed type.
Review the page once again. The
details of the current nominee will appear here.
Check it. After that, go down a little on the page.
Now you have to check the details of the new name nominee.
If you want to change something, then
touch on the edit type and correct it. After that,
touch on the submit button. As soon as you
touch on the submit button, the
name will be updated in your policy and a message of
policy certificate has been updated successfully will appear on your screen. To
download the endorsement certificate of the changes you have made in your policy,
touch here.
And after downloading it, keep it with the policy copy.
A new page will open.
To send the policy copy on WhatsApp, touch here.
If you want to ask for your policy copy on your email ID, then
touch here.
And if you want to download the policy copy and
keep it on your mobile, then
touch the download policy type. As soon as you
touch here, the
endorsement copy will be downloaded. You have to
download the copy from here and
keep it with Manpal Singh copy. In
this way, you cannot update the name.
Thank you.